http://www.happyfeet.com/privacy

0
NewWomen'sNewAll Women's FootwearNatural cork footbeds, premium leather uppers, and fashion forward detailing. From wedges to ankle straps, we’ve got it all.NewSandals
Dressy or Casual, meet our selection of Women's Sandals from the top Comfort Brands on earth.
NewShoesNatural cork footbeds premium leather uppersFashion forward detailing
From wedges to ankle straps, we’ve got it all, Birkenstock, Finn Comfort, Vionic, Dansko and More…
NewClogsClassic European style clogs crafted from ultra rich leathers, suedes, and sustainable cork footbeds. MulesNewBootsLeather ankle boots, suede boots, riding boots, heeled booties - the list goes on and on! Make your boot game strong, supportive, and fun!InsolesInsoles, orthotics, and inserts that provide relief as long as the day. A wide range of styles, shapes, and sizes ensures your glass slipper will never fall off. Shoe Care & AccessoriesBrushes, seals, and scrubs to protect your investment for long lasting, comfortable shoes. NewMen'sNewAll Men's FootwearNewSandalsNewShoesNewClogs
MulesNewBootsInsolesShoe Care & AccessoriesBrushes, seals, and scrubs to protect your investment for long lasting, comfortable shoes. NewInsolesWomen's InsolesFind the perfect fit for your routine and lifestyle. Choose from casual insoles to dressy inserts, ultra cushioned memory foam to classic cork.Men's InsolesFind the perfect fit for your routine and lifestyle. Choose from casual insoles to dressy inserts, ultra cushioned memory foam to classic cork.NewBirkenstockThe original Birkenstock product that started it all, these footbeds offer premium arch support, natural cork, and stabilizing heel cups.Finn ComfortReplaceable insoles for your favorite shoes, sandals, boots, and clogs. Built according to the highest podiatric standards that not only support your feet, but your entire body. Aetrex LyncoAetrex Lynco orthotics offers a wide variety of styles that will compliment your lifestyle. CopperGuard® prevents odor and bacteria while premium memory foam layers provide a cushioned step. KenkohGet the Same Soothing Massage and Great Support that Comes with Our Kenkoh Massage Sandals now in any of Your Existing Shoes!NewWork ShoesKitchenNewMedicalNewBrandsNewAetrexArcopedicoNewBirkenstockNewBrooksNewDanskoNewECCOFinn ComfortNewKenkohKlogsMephistoRevereNewTaosVionicNewKenkohNewMassage SandalsExperience Relief Today! If you suffer from foot,
knee or back pain you need a Kenkoh.
The Kenkoh Massage Sandals use the natural methods of Reflexology to stimulate healthy circulation to your entire body. This reduces swelling and provides vital oxygen to those painful areas. Read what customers are saying, order a pair for yourself and start walking pain free.NewKenkoh ReviewsRead What Kenkoh Customers Are SayingSarah’s StoryRead the Incredible True Story of How One Devoted Kenkoh User Found Relief from Debilitating Diabetic Neuropathy.Experience Relief Today! If you suffer from foot,
knee or back pain you need a Kenkoh.
The Kenkoh Massage Sandals use the natural methods of Reflexology to stimulate healthy circulation to your entire body. This reduces swelling and provides vital oxygen to those painful areas. Read what customers are saying, order a pair for yourself and start walking pain free.SALEGift CardsBuy a Gift CardCheck The Balance of a Gift Card
Store Locator
Account
Wishlist
Sign Up
Email Address
Password
Remember Me
Create Account
Home
::
Customer Service
::
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. Customer e-mail addresses are collected at the time of purchase and added to our e-mail newsletter mailing list. Recipients of newsletter e-mails may opt out at any time by clicking on the "opt out" option at the bottom of all of our e-mails.The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.Your personally identifiable information is kept secure and not sold. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. Our software is PCI compliant. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By E-Mail: CustomerService@HappyFeet.com
By Phone: 1-800-336-6657
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Why Shop With Us?
You’ll receive an email from us soon.
Email
First Name
Subscribe
Site Map | Privacy Policy | © 1985-2020 Happy Feet Plus. All rights reserved.
Back to Top
Please Wait...
X(close)
Get the Latest on Sales, New Shoes,
and News of Everything Healthy.
Thank you for subscribing
You'll receive an email from us soon.
Email Address*
First Name
Submit
